[Music]
Hey class is ringing [Music] Madhura
Madhula is
great Hello Sara Naat come on everyone play
[Music]
Hey Khep
play,
there is
no class, there is
class,
intelligence
too, lungi
dance, lungi dance, lungi dance, lungi dance, lungi dance, lungi
dance
[Music]
give
thank you [Music] you
[Music]
Hey which class, no market, move aside, everyone listen to Holi,
hey class,
you
are
class, everyone literature, the same, the gaadi ke patho bado re Bai, Ru
Ru, read it all, listen, hey
now, the radish lemon ula lemon la lemon la lemon la lemon la lemon la lemon la kata kata, a little bit
lemon la labu
[Laughter]
Gendu, you settle down, you read it, everyone read it [Laughter]
Hey everyone is ready, it's beginning, hey lemonuda, hey lemonuda, hey
lemonuda, a very small raw
lemonuda, come on, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Ru Ru, who all, hey,
you too, song, dance, all,
hey, dance, hey,
sir,
add
[Music]
Hey, which sound should I put on?
Hey,
listen to me, Madhali
[Music]
You are a
spectacle, Papa,
you are all
sir, yours, yours is the
sound, the pub is
not right, scoundrel, see the
benefit.